pinchme.com.au 2013-06-21

# Privacy Policy - PINCHme | Free Samples from Top Brands

## PINCHme Australia Pty Ltd (ABN 82 155 902 891) (referred to as "PINCHme", "we", "us" or "our") acknowledges and respects the privacy of personal information and is committed to the protection of the personal information that we hold. This policy sets out the way in which we will use, manage and protect your personal information in accordance with applicable Australian privacy legislation.

By providing your personal information to us and by using the PINCHme Website on [pinchme.com.au] ("Website") you agree to this Privacy Policy. We may review and update this Privacy Policy from time to time to take account of new laws and technology, changes to our operations and practices and the changing business environment. All personal information held by us will be governed by our most recent Privacy Policy. The most recent Privacy Policy will always be available on our Website.

### What information do we collect?

We only collect personal information that is necessary for us to conduct our business (including our Loyalty Program) and for us to comply with our policies and procedures. The nature of the personal information we collect will be dependent upon your chosen level of interaction with PINCHme, and, if you become a PINCHme Member, the degree to which you utilise your PINCHme membership and the benefits, products and services available to you under your membership.

If you become a PINCHme Member, the following information may be collected:

  * your name, address, email address, Year of birth , gender, , and contact information including your mobile phone number;
  * Primary grocery shopping location
  * other personal information you may disclose to us when you request information from us, or that is contained in communications between us and you, including Sensitive Information.

### How we collect and hold personal information

PINCHme collects most personal information directly from you. We usually collect personal information in the following ways:

  * when you visit our website;
  * when you respond to a survey we send you;
  * when you provide information by email or in letters or other documents;
  * when someone refers you to us (eg: email address)

We hold personal information in electronic and hard copy files.

### Collection of information from PINCHme Website

When using the Website you may voluntarily disclose personal information to us. Our server may automatically record details such as your internet address, domain name and the date and time of your visit to our website. We use this information for statistical purposes.

We also use this information in order to provide you with a personalised experience when you visit the Website. Through the use of a cookie (a small data file that a website may write to your hard drive when you visit it), we can record the pages you visit and the information you require. Through analysis of these records, we provide you with an improved service when you revisit the website.

Many internet browsers are set up so that they accept cookies. You may be able to change these settings so that cookies are not accepted or you are provided with options to accept or reject them as they are sent to your browser.

### Why we collect personal information and consequences of not providing it to us

Generally, we collect personal information to validate your identity, to process your application for membership, to meet our obligations to you and to enable us to conduct our business. We also collect personal information so you can receive products offered by us, receive other special offers, join our loyalty program, complete a survey or questionnaire, enter a competition,[seek employment or communicate with PINCHme by e-mail, telephone or writing.

If you do not wish to give us personal information then our ability to process your Membership application, meet our obligations to you or provide goods, services or information to you may be adversely affected.

### How we use your personal information and when we disclose it

PINCHme may use your personal information for a variety of purposes in connection with providing you with products and services (and information on opportunities to obtain these products or services) and special offers available to PINCHme Members.

In addition, PINCHme may also use your personal information to:

  * provide offers to persons who register as a Member to receive information on opportunities to obtain products or services;
  * to process, manage and administer the products and services PINCHme provides to you;
  * to develop processes, products and services to better meet your needs;
  * to help PINCHme manage and enhance its products and services and the opportunities to obtain products or services;
  * to promote and market other products or services of PINCHme that you may be interested in;
  * unless requested not to, to send you marketing materials which promote the goods or services of a third party (including by way of electronic direct marketing activities);
  * unless requested not to, to provide your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.
  * 

If you do not wish to receive information about third party products and services please let us know. Contact details are set out below.

We may disclose personal information for the purpose for which it was collected and also:

  * to organisations who are involved with or participating in a product or service that is provided by PINCHme or in a promotional campaign, competition or survey to related bodies corporate of PINCHme for the purpose of conducting business;
  * to any contractor PINCHme engages to provide services for PINCHme including IT services, mailing services, distribution services, data analysis, research, advertising or consultancy services;
  * to our professional advisers;
  * to regulatory authorities;
  * where required or authorised by law; and
  * where you consent to the disclosure.

The disclosure of information to the parties listed above may involve the transfer of your personal information to a foreign country. If we collect any personal information from you, you explicitly consent to this transfer. eg: we will be using offshore data storage for backup and security.

We may from time to time publish information on the Website about certain Members. However, this information will be limited to the Member's first name and the suburb the Member nominates in its delivery address with the post code. Where we conduct competitions on the Website or through social media the terms and conditions of the competition will include its own privacy provisions.

PINCHme may decide to buy or sell assets which form part of or relate to its business. In any such transaction, personal information will usually be one of the transferred assets and will be disclosed to the purchaser.

### Sensitive Information

Some personal information which PINCHme collects may be "sensitive information". Sensitive information includes: information relating to a person's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, membership of a political association, religious beliefs or affiliations, philosophical beliefs, trade union or other professional or trade association membership, sexual preferences and criminal record, that is also personal information; health information and genetic information about an individual.

Sensitive Information will be used and disclosed only for the purpose for which it was provided or a directly related secondary purpose, unless you agree otherwise, or where certain other limited circumstances apply (eg, where required by law).

### Security of personal information

Irrespective of whether personal information is stored electronically or in hard copy form, we take reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuseand loss and unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

### Access and correction

You have a right to access personal information we hold about you, subject to some exceptions allowed by law. We will comply with any such request except where the Privacy Act 1988 or the National Privacy Principles allow us to refuse to do so. There is no fee for making such a request, but we may charge for providing access.

We take all reasonable precautions to ensure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date. However, the accuracy of that information depends to a large extent upon the information you provide. If any personal information you provide to us changes, please let us know. Contact details are set out below.

### Privacy Complaints

If you wish to complain about any breach or potential breach of this Privacy Policy or the National Privacy Principles, please contact us. Contact details are set out below. Complaints will be considered within 21 days and responded to. We will always endeavour to resolve any complaint to your satisfaction, however, if you are unhappy with our response, you are entitled to contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner, which may investigate your complaint further.

### Contact details

If you would like to send us any questions about privacy issues, have any concerns about privacy or wish to make a complaint about any breach or potential breach of this Privacy Policy or the National Privacy Principles, please contact us at privacy@pinchme.com.au or write to us at the address below.

PINCHme Australia Pty Ltd  
Suite 501A, 19A Boundary Street,  
Rushcutters Bay, NSW 2011  
Attention: Chief Operations Officer

### Definitions

The terms "Loyalty Program" and "Member" have the meanings given to them in the PINCHme Website Terms and Conditions.
